tightvnc.com 2018-12-20

# TightVNC Website: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy and Information on Cookies

In our company, GlavSoft LLC, **we fully respect your privacy**. While you are visiting our website, submitting forms from its webpages, sending us email messages or correspond with us in other ways, we may gather certain types of information, and this document explains the types of information we collect, what we do with it and how to correct, change or delete your information. 

One special type of privacy-sensitive information is **“cookies”**. Their use is also described in this document, please see the section “Cookies and Website Analytics” below. 

Please use our website, our services and products only if you agree with this Privacy Policy. 

### Requesting Information via Web Forms or by Email

When you request information on licensing our products, we collect your name, email address, company name, your position at the company, and a list of products you are interested in. We need this information to send you email messages, address you properly, determine if your company is already our current or prospective customer, check if you have effective licenses or active maintenance contracts, and send you information on products and services you are interested in. The information listed above, as well as additional information you will provide in email discussion, may be saved in the database of our prospective customers, and may be used to send you emails with information relevant to the list of products you are interested in, including offers to purchase our products and services. 

### Purchasing Our Products and Services

When you purchase our products or services, we may collect your name and contact details, information about the items purchased, details of your subscription to our services, and other payment-related information, as sent by you to our company directly or gathered from you by payment site or financial institution and transferred to us. 

This information is used to identify you or your company as our customer, deliver documents, license keys and products, including new versions of products, offer purchased services, provide technical support, send important information about purchased products and services, renew purchased subscriptions, inform about expiration dates or changed terms, or perform other actions if they are part of our agreements or are defined by the nature of our product or service. 

### Cookies and Website Analytics

To improve your experience on our site, we may use “cookies”. Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. 

Cookies are used for two particular purposes on our site: (1) to enable Google Analytics, and (2) to remember that you were informed about cookies on our website, so that we would not have to show cookie-related warnings repeatedly, each time you open any of our webpages. 

Google Analytics is a service which allows us to analyse usage of our website. It transmits website traffic statistics to Google servers. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to understand website traffic and webpage usage. Google Analytics cannot work without using cookies. 

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse corresponding cookies, disable JavaScript, or [use the opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

### Social Media

If you share our content through social media, for example by liking us on Facebook, following or tweeting about us on Twitter, or giving us a “+1” via Google Plus, those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose. 

In some cases, where a page on our website includes content from a social network, such as a Twitter feed, or Facebook comments box, those services may set a cookie even where you do not click a button. As is the case for all cookies, we cannot access those set by social networks, just as those social networks cannot access cookies we set ourselves. 

### Log Files

Similarly to almost all other websites, our systems automatically gather anonymous information about visitors of the website, including IP addresses, browser types, languages, the times and dates of webpage visits, general locations as determined from IP addresses and provided by the browser, the sites from which visitors come. 

The data collected does not include personally identifiable information and may be used for statistical analysis, to understand user behaviour, and to administer the site. This information is removed automatically after fixed period of time (not exceeding two months) as specified in the configuration of the web server software used to host our website. 

### Disclosing to Third Parties

Your information will not be disclosed to any third party unless you have given your consent to such disclosure, or that's a part of the agreement or contract between you and our company. 

### Sale of Business

In a special case, if our business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers, and will be passed on to the new owners of the business. The information will be disclosed only to the extent required for business sale procedures, and will be protected by non-disclosure agreements with all parties involved. 

### Control Your Information

You have the right to know what personal information we are holding on you. Also, you may ask us to correct or change your information, or choose to remove its particular parts, or delete all your information completely. In any of these cases, please send us an email requesting the action desired. Please see our email addresses on the [“Contact Us” page on our web site](https://www.tightvnc.com/contact.php). 

Please note that if you use any of our products or services which require you to provide personal information, deleting our records may mean that you will need to resubmit it to continue using such products or services.
